Princeton Football Films Collection, 1935-2012(bulk 1935-1990): Finding Aid AC297
University Archives
- Princeton Football Film Reels, 1935-1990; 2187 items
  - 1988-1990, 262 items
    - 1988 Bucknell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Bucknell (Kicking))
    - 1988 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1988 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1988 Colgate (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Full Game 1))
    - 1988 Colgate (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Full Game 2))
    - 1988 Colgate (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Full Game 3))
    - 1988 Colgate (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Full Game 4))
    - 1988 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1988 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1988 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1988 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1988 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1988 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1988 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1988 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1988 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1988 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1988 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1988 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1988 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1988 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1988 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1988 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1988 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1988 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1988 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1988 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1988 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1988 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1988 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1988 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1988 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1988 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1988 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1988 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1988 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1988 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1988 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1988 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1988 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1988 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1988 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1988 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1988 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1988 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1988 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1988 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1988 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1988 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1988 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1988 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1988 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1988 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1988 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1988 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1988 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1988 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1988 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1988 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1988 Holy Cross (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Holy Cross (Defense 1))
    - 1988 Holy Cross (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Holy Cross (Defense 2))
    - 1988 Holy Cross (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Holy Cross (Full Game 1))
    - 1988 Holy Cross (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Holy Cross (Full Game 2))
    - 1988 Holy Cross (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1988 Holy Cross (Full Game 3))
    - 1988 Holy Cross (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1988 Holy Cross (Full Game 4))
    - 1988 Holy Cross (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Holy Cross (Kicking))
    - 1988 Holy Cross (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Holy Cross (Kicking))
    - 1988 Holy Cross (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Holy Cross (Offense 1))
    - 1988 Holy Cross (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Holy Cross (Offense 2))
    - 1988 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1988 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1988 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1988 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1988 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1988 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1988 Penn (Full Game 5), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Full Game 5))
    - 1988 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1988 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1988 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1988 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1988 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1988 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1988 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1988 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1988 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1988 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1988 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1988 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1988 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1988 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1989 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1989 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1989 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1989 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1989 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1989 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1989 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1989 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1989 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1989 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1989 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1989 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1989 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1989 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1989 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1989 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1989 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1989 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1989 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1989 Fordham (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Defense 1))
    - 1989 Fordham (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Defense 2))
    - 1989 Fordham (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Defense 2))
    - 1989 Fordham (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Full Game 1))
    - 1989 Fordham (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Full Game 2))
    - 1989 Fordham (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Full Game 3))
    - 1989 Fordham (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Full Game 4))
    - 1989 Fordham (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Kicking))
    - 1989 Fordham (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Kicking))
    - 1989 Fordham (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Offense 1))
    - 1989 Fordham (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Fordham (Offense 2))
    - 1989 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1989 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1989 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1989 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1989 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1989 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1989 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1989 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1989 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1989 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1989 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1989 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Defense 1))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Defense 2))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Full Game 1))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Full Game 2))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Full Game 3))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Full Game 4))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Kicking))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Kicking))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Offense 1))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Offense 1))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Offense 2))
    - 1989 Holy Cross (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Holy Cross (Offense 2))
    - 1989 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1989 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1989 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1989 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1989 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1989 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1989 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1989 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1989 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1989 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Defense 1))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Defense 1))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Defense 2))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Full Game 1))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Full Game 2))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Kicking))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Kicking))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Offense 1))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Offense 1))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Offense 2))
    - 1989 William and Mary (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 William and Mary (Offense 2))
    - 1989 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1989 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1989 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1989 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1989 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1989 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1989 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1989 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1989 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1989 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1989 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1989 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1989 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1990 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1990 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1990 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1990 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Bucknell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Bucknell (Defense 1))
    - 1990 Bucknell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Bucknell (Defense 2))
    - 1990 Bucknell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Bucknell (Kicking))
    - 1990 Bucknell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Bucknell (Kicking))
    - 1990 Bucknell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Bucknell (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Bucknell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Bucknell (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1990 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1990 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1990 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1990 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1990 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1990 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1990 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1990 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1990 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1990 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1990 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1990 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1990 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1990 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1990 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1990 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Fordham (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Fordham (Defense 1))
    - 1990 Fordham (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Fordham (Defense 2))
    - 1990 Fordham (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Fordham (Kicking))
    - 1990 Fordham (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Fordham (Kicking))
    - 1990 Fordham (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Fordham (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Fordham (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Fordham (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1990 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1990 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1990 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1990 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1990 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1990 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1990 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1990 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1990 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1990 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1990 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1990 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1990 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1990 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1990 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1990 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1990 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1989 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - Cornell (No. 1), 1989; 1 item (Item Cornell (No. 1))
    - 1989 Cornell (Kicks), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Kicks))
    - 1989 Cornell (Ivy League Champions, 3), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Ivy League Champions, 3))
    - 1989 Cornell (Ivy League Champions, 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Ivy League Champions, 1))
    - 1989 Cornell (Ivy League Champions, 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Ivy League Champions, 2))
    - 1989 Cornell (Offense 1, print), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Offense 1, print))
    - 1989 Cornell (Offense 1, original), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Offense 1, original))
    - 1989 Cornell (Ivy League Champions, 4), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Ivy League Champions, 4))
    - 1989 Cornell (Kicks, print), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Kicks, print))
    - 1989 Cornell (Defense, 2), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Defense, 2))
    - 1989 Cornell (Defense, 1), 1 item (Item 1989 Cornell (Defense, 1))
- Princeton Football Videos, 2012 Season, 1 box
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  AR.2012.146
  No arrangement action taken or arrangement information not recorded at the time of processing.
  The video footage of the 2012 Princeton varsity football team includes a comeback victory over Harvard (Princeton scored 29 points in the last 13 minutes); and a win at Yale that gave Princeton its first Big 3 championship since 2006.
  - Princeton Football Videos, 2012 Season DVDs, 1 box
    - Princeton vs. Lehigh, 9-15-12, O/D/K, 2012; 1 box (Box 1)
    - Princeton vs. Georgetown, 9-22-12, O/D/K, 2012; 1 box (Box 1)
    - Princeton vs. Columbia, 9-27-12, O/D/K, 2012; 1 box (Box 1)
    - Princeton vs. Lafayette, 10-6-12, O/D/K, 2012; 1 box (Box 1)
    - Princeton vs. Brown, 10-13-12, O/D/K, 2012; 1 box (Box 1)
    - Princeton vs. Harvard, 10-20-12, O/D/K, 1 box (Box 1)
    - Princeton vs. Cornell, 10-27-12, O/D/K, 2012; 1 box (Box 1)
    - Princeton vs. Pennsylvania, 11-3-12, O/D/K, 2012; 1 box (Box 1)
    - Princeton vs. Yale, 11-10-12, O/D/K, 2012; 1 box (Box 1)
    - Princeton vs. Dartmouth, 11-17-12, O/D/K, 2012; 1 box (Box 1)
- Princeton Freshman (Frosh) Football Film Reels, 1922-2001; 671 items
  Series 3 contains original film reels (mostly 16 mm or 8 mm) documenting Princeton freshman (frosh) football games between 1951 and 2001. For many games more than one reel exists, documenting only offense or defensive plays, practices or scrimmages, kicking, or specific quarters of the game. Duplicate prints of certain reels are also included in the collection.
  During a survey of the Princeton Freshman (Frosh) Football Film Reels in January of 2020, film descriptions were transcribed from existing enclosures. Some descriptions indicated non-football related films. Description accuracy could not be confirmed at this time, therefore the potentially unrealted reels remain in the collection.
  - Princeton Frosh vs. Penn. Frosh, 10/25/74 - 2nd Quarter, 1974; 1 item (Item 1)
  - Columbia Freshman vs. Princeton University, 175-176 - Defense 1, undated; 1 item (Item 2)
  - Princeton Frosh vs. Penn. Frosh, 10/25/74 - 1st Quarter, 1974; 1 item (Item 3)
  - Princeton Frosh vs. Penn. Frosh, 11/4/78 - Kicks, 1978; 1 item (Item 4)
  - Freshmen Princeton vs. Columbia, 10/4/1974 - Reel #2, 1 item (Item 5)
  - Princeton Frosh vs. Penn. Frosh, 10/23/70 - 1st Quarter Print, 1970; 1 item (Item 6)
  - Princeton Frosh vs. Penn. Frosh, 10/23/70 - 2nd Quarter Print, 1970; 1 item (Item 7)
  - Princeton Frosh vs. Penn. Frosh, 10/23/70 - 3rd Quarter Print, 1970; 1 item (Item 8)
  - Princeton Frosh vs. Penn. Frosh, 10/23/70 - 4th Quarter Print, 1970; 1 item (Item 9)
  - Princeton Frosh vs. Penn. Frosh, 10/23/74 - 4th Quarter Print, 1974; 1 item (Item 10)
  - Princeton Glassboro St. #2, 9/24/79, 1979; 1 item (Item 11)
  - Princeton Glassboro St. #1, 9/24/79, 1979; 1 item (Item 12)
  - Princeton Williams OFF. #2, 9/15/79, 1979; 1 item (Item 13)
  - Princeton Williams OFF. #1, 9/15/79, 1979; 1 item (Item 14)
  - Princeton Williams DEF. #1, 9/15/79, 1979; 1 item (Item 15)
  - Princeton Williams DEF. #2, 9/15/79, 1979; 1 item (Item 16)
  - Princeton Williams - Kicks, 9/15/79, 1979; 1 item (Item 17)
  - Princeton University vs. Dartmouth OFF #1, 1980, 1 item (Item 18)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia DEF. #2, 10/10/81, 1981; 1 item (Item 19)
  - Princeton vs. Yale DEF. #1 Orig., 11/14/81, 1981; 1 item (Item 20)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia DEF. #1, 10/10/81, 1981; 1 item (Item 21)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia OFF. #2, 10/10/82, 1981; 1 item (Item 22)
  - Princeton vs. Dartmouth OFF. #1, 10/4/81, 1981; 1 item (Item 23)
  - Princeton vs. Dartmouth OFF. #2, 10/4/81, 1981; 1 item (Item 24)
  - Yale/Princeton Freshmen 3, 11/12/66, 1966; 1 item (Item 25)
  - Yale/Princeton Freshmen 4, 11/12/66, 1966; 1 item (Item 26)
  - Yale/Princeton Freshmen 2, 11/12/66, 1966; 1 item (Item 27)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 10/24/64, 1964; 1 item (Item 28)
  - Yale/Princeton Freshmen 1, 10/12/66, 1966; 1 item (Item 29)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Harvard Fr. 1, 11/5/66, 1966; 1 item (Item 30)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Harvard Fr. 3, 11/5/66, 1966; 1 item (Item 31)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Harvard Fr. 2, 11/5/66, 1966; 1 item (Item 32)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 10/25/69 - Reel #1, 1969; 1 item (Item 33)
  - Princeton vs. U. of P. Fr., 11/4/61, 1961; 1 item (Item 34)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Yale Fr., 11/18/61 - Reel #2, 1961; 1 item (Item 35)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 11/3/62, 1962; 1 item (Item 36)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Harvard, 11/9/63 - Reel #2, 1 item (Item 37)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Harvard, 11/9/63 - Reel #1, 1 item (Item 38)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 11/3/62 - Reel #3, 1962; 1 item (Item 39)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 11/3/62 - Reel #2, 1962; 1 item (Item 40)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 10/30/76 - 2nd Qt. Defense and 2nd Half Defense, 1976; 1 item (Item 41)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 9/10/76 - 2nd Half Defense, 1976; 1 item (Item 42)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 10/30/76 - 2nd Half Defense, 1976; 1 item (Item 43)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 10/30/76 - 1st Half Defense, 1976; 1 item (Item 44)
  - Princeton vs. Millersville, 9/9/76 - 2nd Half Offense, 1976; 1 item (Item 45)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 10/30/76 - 1st Half Offense, 1976; 1 item (Item 46)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia, 10/10/81 - Offense 1, 1981; 1 item (Item 47)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia, 10/10/81 - Kicks, 1981; 1 item (Item 48)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Columbia, 10/10/80 - DEF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 49)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 11/1/58, 1958; 1 item (Item 50)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard, 10/24/81 - OFF. #2 Print, 1981; 1 item (Item 51)
  - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/81 - DEF. #2, 1981; 1 item (Item 52)
  - Princeton/Cornell, 9/20/80 - OFF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 53)
  - Princeton/Cornell, 9/20/80 - OFF. #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 54)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn, 11/3/84 - OFF. #2, 1984; 1 item (Item 55)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn, 11/3/84 - Kicks, 1984; 1 item (Item 56)